<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cores on HerdWare</title>
    <link>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cores on HerdWare</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Abondance core</title>
      <link>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/abondance/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/abondance/index.html</guid>
      <description>Name origin Image&#39;s source.  Abondance is a french breed of cows from the Haute-Savoie in the south-east of France. It is mainly raised for its milk used in multiple cheeses like the Reblochon, the Abondance and others.
  This page and the following ones describe the Abondance core. It is a multiple issue out-of-order CPU with two levels of cache memories.
Overview   
Figure 1: Overview of the the Abondance core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aubrac core</title>
      <link>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/aubrac/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/aubrac/index.html</guid>
      <description>Name origin Image&#39;s source.  Aubrac is a french breed of cows from the Plateau de l&amp;rsquo;Aubrac in the south-central of France. It is mainly raised for its meat, but also for its milk which can be used for the Laguiole cheese.
  This page and the following ones describe the Aubrac core. It is single issue in-order CPU build around a classic pipeline and two levels of cache memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salers core</title>
      <link>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/salers/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://herd-ware.github.io/doc/hw/cores/salers/index.html</guid>
      <description>  Warning The Salers code the code is currently revised before being made available on GitHub. Do not hesitate to ask if you want information.
   Name origin Image&#39;s source.  Salers is a french breed of cows from the Cantal in the south-central of France. It is raised for its meat but also its milk used in the Salers cheese.
  Overview ISA support Table of contents  </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>